<extensions>
	<details>
		<title lang="EN">AF-1 Repo</title>
	</details>
	<plugins>
		<plugin name="AlternativePlayCount" version="0.3.11" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Alternative Play Count</title>
			<desc lang="EN">Intended as a companion plugin for 'Dynamic Playlists 3' and 'Visual Statistics'. Provides alternative play counts and skip counts that aim to reflect your true listening history. You set a time after which a song counts as played. Create (scheduled) backups, restore from backups. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-alternativeplaycount/releases/download/0.3.11/lms-alternativeplaycount-0.3.11.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-alternativeplaycount</link>
			<sha>9c087260cc1a36877b4c0c353b40a725c72af18c</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="CustomSkip3" version="3.2.0" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Custom Skip 3</title>
			<desc lang="EN">This plugin lets you define client-specific filter sets with rules for when tracks should be skipped automatically. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-customskip/releases/download/3.2.0/lms-customskip-3.2.0.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-customskip#faq</link>
			<sha>dbf001e7b7d7f0be1eef61ddc505e213b5cd5801</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="CustomStartStopTimes" version="0.1.6" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Custom Start Stop Times</title>
			<desc lang="EN">This plugin allows you to start and stop tracks at a specified playback/song time. Just add custom start and stop times to a track's comments tag and, with the help of this plugin, the song will start and end, i.e. skip to the next one, when you want it to. No more annoying song intros or minutes of silence at the end. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-customstartstoptimes/releases/download/0.1.6/lms-customstartstoptimes-0.1.6.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-customstartstoptimes</link>
			<sha>4969dca335b25ab01ce1963e305ead3812d13dce</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="DynamicPlaylists3" version="3.6.7" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Dynamic Playlists 3</title>
			<desc lang="EN">This plugin lets you play continuous music mixes based on selection criteria defined in so-called dynamic playlists. Comes with a number of ready-to-use dynamic playlists and new playlist parameters. In addition you can now use your own custom dynamic playlist definitions directly in DPL without intermediary plugins. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<desc lang="FR">Ce plugin permet de jouer des mix continus de musique basés sur des critères de sélection définis dans les listes de lecture dynamiques. Vient avec un ensemble de listes de lecture dynamiques prêtes à l'emploi. En addition vous pouvez maintenant utiliser vos propres listes de lecture dynamiques directement dans DPL sans plugin intermédiaire. Plus d'information sur la page GitHub.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-dynamicplaylists/releases/download/3.6.7/lms-dynamicplaylists-3.6.7.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-dynamicplaylists#faq</link>
			<sha>2606bd3cfdca00cd6e369f989156a70c7ca59260</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="RatingsLight" version="2.2.1" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Ratings Light</title>
			<desc lang="EN">A plugin that takes care of rating your tracks. Set track ratings (also with plugins/apps and IR remote). Import track ratings from file tags or playlists. Export track ratings to playlist files. Create (scheduled) backups, restore from backups. Create virtual libraries for (top) rated tracks. Browse (top) rated tracks by artist or genre (browse menus). Keep track of your recently rated songs with a dedicated playlist or log file. Show rated songs for artist, album, genre, year or playlist (context menu). Support for online library tracks where possible. Includes "Don't Stop The Music" mixes. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-ratingslight/releases/download/2.2.1/lms-ratingslight-2.2.1.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-ratingslight</link>
			<sha>f8ce53f5e6afd7533f2b07335c9483a0173b46d8</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="SQLiteVirtualLibraries" version="0.4.1" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">SQLite Virtual Libraries</title>
			<desc lang="EN">Create your own virtual libraries using files with an SQLite statement and create browse menus for any LMS virtual library, incl. those not created with SQLVL. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-sqlitevirtuallibraries/releases/download/0.4.1/lms-sqlitevirtuallibraries-0.4.1.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-sqlitevirtuallibraries</link>
			<sha>6d55e6afb207371b0dbee1d2779cd65abfdc7657</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="UseCommentTagInfo" version="1.3.9" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Use Comment Tag Info</title>
			<desc lang="EN">This plugin uses (key)words in your music files' comment tags to: add extra information to the song details page, define and display custom title formats, create virtual libraries with browse menus. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-usecommenttaginfo/releases/download/1.3.9/lms-usecommenttaginfo-1.3.9.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-usecommenttaginfo</link>
			<sha>a36b759fce91b9baa6d2de77ca4f5cf6c991b874</sha>
		</plugin>


		<plugin name="VisualStatistics" version="1.4.10" minTarget="7.9" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">Visual Statistics</title>
			<desc lang="EN">Have a look at your library statistics with charts. More information on the GitHub page.</desc>
			<desc lang="FR">Explorez les statistiques de votre librairie avec des graphiques. Plus d'information sur la page GitHub.</desc>
			<desc lang="NL">Bekijk jouw mediabibliotheek statistieken door middel van grafieken</desc>
			<url>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-visualstatistics/releases/download/1.4.10/lms-visualstatistics-1.4.10.zip</url>
			<creator>AF</creator>
			<link>https://github.com/AF-1/lms-visualstatistics</link>
			<sha>b68f8a0c198455061cb3ec24639589e5e4a4e972</sha>
		</plugin>
	</plugins>
</extensions>
